{"data":[{"question":"Did you ________ to the theater when you lived in London?","a":"use to go","b":"used to go","c":"use to going","d":"used to going","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true \n- Interrogative form: Did + S + use to Verb ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"We ________ in London, but now we live in Bristol.","a":"use to live","b":"used to live","c":"used to living","d":"use to living","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There ________ an old castle near the lake.","a":"used to be","b":"use to be","c":"used to being","d":"use to being","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"You can never ________ to the noise of the traffic.","a":"get used","b":"get use","c":"getting used","d":"getting use","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: don't\/doesn't\/can't\/didn't\/hasn't\/haven't get\/got + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"When I lived in London I used ________ to the cinema very often.","a":"go","b":"to go","c":"going","d":"to going","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't smoke now, but I ________ a lot.","a":"used to smoking","b":"use to smoking","c":"used to smoke","d":"use to smoke","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Used to Verb:\n\n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past.\n\n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There ________ an old house here.","a":"use to be","b":"used to being","c":"used to be","d":"use to being","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true \n- There used to be an old house here= In the past, there was an old house here but now the house is no longer here","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He ________ a lot but now he stays at home.","a":"used to travel","b":"use to travel","c":"used to travelling","d":"use to travelling","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Used to Verb: \n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past. \n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"They are not ________ to work so early.","a":"used to go","b":"use to go","c":"used to going","d":"use to going","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"The climate here is very hot, and I'm not used ________.","a":"to hot","b":"the heat","c":"to such heat","d":"the hot","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...\n\n- Negative form: don't\/doesn't\/can't\/didn't\/hasn't\/haven't get\/got + used to Verb_ing\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}